Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
Edwin and Terry Murray Comic Book Collection
- Additions (2010-0071 and 2010-0107) 1966-2009, (5 boxes)
  - Bill Black's Fun Comics, Issue 3
1990s: Publisher: Millennium Box: 431
1990s: Publisher: Monster Box: 431
1990s: Publisher: Northstar Publishing Box: 432
1990s: Publisher: Palliard Press Box: 432
1990s: Publisher: Pure Imagination Box: 434
1990s: Publisher: Quality Box: 435
1990s: Publisher: Russ Cochran Box: 438
1990s: Publisher: Special Studio Box: 438
1990s: Publisher: Tekno Box: 439
1990s: Publisher: Tome Press Box: 439
1990s: Publisher: Topps Box: 439, 440
1990s: Publisher: T.S.R. Box: 440
1990s: Publisher: Valiant Box: 441-445
1990s: Publisher: Warp Box: 446, 447
1990s: Publisher: Wild Storm Box: 449
1990s: Publisher: Windjammer Box: 449
1990s: Publisher: Wolf Box: 449
2000s: Publisher: Dark Horse Box: 347-348, 350-353
2000s: Publisher: DC Box: 133-138, 143-147, 155, 156, 157, 165-176
2000s: Publisher: Homage Box: 415
2000s: Publisher: Image Box: 419, 420
2000s: Publisher: Kenzer and Company Box: 424
2000s: Publisher: Marvel Box: 237-261, 304-305
2000s: Publisher: Studio Foglio Box: 439
2000s: Publisher: Wild Storm Box: 449